<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Middle-Aged Man Yells at the Cloud</title><link>https://jafd.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Middle-Aged Man Yells at the Cloud</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&amp;copy; 2019&amp;ndash;2020 jafd aka Grumpy Programmer</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jafd.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Looks like KDE is finally usable</title><link>https://jafd.github.io/posts/2020/01/looks-like-kde-is-finally-usable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jafd.github.io/posts/2020/01/looks-like-kde-is-finally-usable/</guid><description>Looks like KDE is finally doing the right thing with their 5.18 Plasma desktop.
First, it looks consistent for the first time in years.
Then, its shell is written in something else than Javascript, and it looks like it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have the mad memory leaks GNOME&amp;rsquo;s Mutter is famous for.
And then, it&amp;rsquo;s not bloated, and seems to do the right thing with multi-monitor configurations.
Haven&amp;rsquo;t yet tried it under Wayland, but I expect it to perform there as well.</description></item><item><title>Music Is Being Eaten by the Cloud</title><link>https://jafd.github.io/posts/2019/10/music-is-being-eaten-by-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jafd.github.io/posts/2019/10/music-is-being-eaten-by-the-cloud/</guid><description>The other day I tried to put my music collection onto some kind of NAS so I could use it from any computer on my network.
It turned out, that while it wasn&amp;rsquo;t much of a problem finding a server to index and serve the music directory over the network, finding a client that is not ancient was more trouble.
Ironically, Apple&amp;rsquo;s own DAAP protocol is not supported by anything produced by Apple anymore.</description></item><item><title>Nice try, Apple, but nope</title><link>https://jafd.github.io/posts/2019/10/nice-try-apple-but-nope/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jafd.github.io/posts/2019/10/nice-try-apple-but-nope/</guid><description>So, Apple has issued a statement that its sharing of the user&amp;rsquo;s browser history with Tencent is limited to users from mainland China. Nice try, but not good enough until they actually clarify that in their terms of protection from fraudulent sites, which still say the same as before:
Before visiting a website, Safari may send information calculated from the website address to Google Safe Browsing and Tencent Safe Browsing to check if the website is fraudulent.</description></item><item><title>This site doesn't use cookies</title><link>https://jafd.github.io/posts/2019/09/this-site-doesnt-use-cookies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jafd.github.io/posts/2019/09/this-site-doesnt-use-cookies/</guid><description>This site doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to offer you a better experience, because the one you get is the best ever. You cannot improve on perfection.</description></item></channel></rss>